{
    "id": "ed0794757d5949cb915f3bd969b62f72",
    "title": "Make compound sentences",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "b65355e44dfa409ab92405d400309e37",
            "title": "Compound Sentences",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I called her many times ........................................... she didnâ€™t answer the phone.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "and",
                        "but",
                        "though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is intelligent ...................................... honest.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "or",
                        "but",
                        "and"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is old ............................................ he is active.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "and",
                        "or",
                        "but"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He not only lost his reputation ........................................... brought a bad name to his family.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "also",
                        "but",
                        "but also"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You may .................................................. spend the night here or go home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "neither",
                        "either",
                        "nor"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I reached the counter ............................................... took my purse out ........................................... there was no money in it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "and, but",
                        "and, and",
                        "but, but",
                        "but, and"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The way may be long ........................................... we may feel tired ............................................ we will not give up hope.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "and, but",
                        "and, and",
                        "but, but"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We took part in the competition ................................................ we did not win any prize.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "and",
                        "but",
                        "or"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Our servant is slow .............................................. he is honest and dependable.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "and",
                        "but",
                        "although"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Leave the house at once ............................................... I will call the police.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "and",
                        "but",
                        "or"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}